Guide to the National Federation of Grain Cooperatives records, 1946-1976.
National Federation of Grain Cooperatives records,
- Series V. Assorted Materials
  - Cooperative, Grange League Federation (GLF), 1951-1965 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Correspondence; Norval G. Budd, New York State, Agway
  - Mid-States Terminals, Toledo, Ohio; Clayton W. Johnson (Box 8?, Folder ?)
  - Corn Referendum, 1954, 1956 (Box 8?, Folder 9)
    Items on feed situation
  - Corn Referendum, 1956, 1958 (Box 8?, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, reports, news releases
  - Corn Advisory Committee, 1953 (Box 8?, Folder 11)
    Reports, comments on price support plan; Fred Maywald, Iowa
  - Cost Price Squeeze Statement, Farmers Union, 1961-03-29 (Box 8?, Folder 12)
    Mimeograph with notes
  - Cotton, 1956-1964 (Box 8?, Folder 13)
    Printed matter, etc. concerning cotton
  - Cotton Producers Association - Birdsey Flour Mills Case, 1965 (Box 8?, Folder 14)
  - "Country Gentleman" - Roy F. Hendrickson, 1948-1953 (Box 8?, Folder 15)
  - Cropland Adjustment Program, 1961 (Box 8?, Folder 16)
    Proposal of Ohio Farm Bureau, mimeograph
  - Crop Prospects, 1963-1964 (Box 8?, Folder 17)
    Europe, other parts of the world
  - Darrow, Wayne - "Ways of Lifting Farm Income" Speech, St. Paul, 1955 (Box 8?, Folder 18)
  - Davidson, Walter A., 1963 (Box 8?, Folder 19)
    Speech, memo on Bruce J. Hend meeting with Davidson and eltter to Davidson from Roy F. Hendrickson on cooperatives and wheat grades
  - Delmarva Soybean Plant, Virginia, 1963 (Box 8?, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, hearings, exhibits
  - Cooperative Oil Mills - Reports, Minutes, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Oilseeds Association, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Correspondence on forming oilseed association, several informative letters
  - Cooperatives, 1955-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Various mimeograph and printed matter on cooperatives
  - Cooperative Soybeans, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Printed matter, etc. concerning meeting, Canada
  - M.W. Thatcher - Committee of Agriculture, 1954-03-25 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - M.W. Thatcher Letter to Clifford R. Hope - Grain, Importation of Grain, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - M.W. Thatcher Statement before Senate Committee on Agriculture - Farm Legislation, 1954-04-07 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - M.W. Thatcher - O.F. Theimer - Grain Storage, Immigration, Germany, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - M.W. Thatcher, Montana Farmers Union - Farm Legislation, 1964-10 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Robert L. Thatcher - Rural Health, 19th National Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Farmers Union Grain Terminal Association - Paul R. Thatcher, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Farmers Union Grain Terminal Association - Thomas F. Toohey, Feed Grains, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Farmers Union Grain Terminal Association - Charles H. Wulff, Transportation and Dry Bulk Commodity, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Farmers Union Grain Terminal Association - M.J. Werner, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Farmers Union Grain Terminal Elevator, Incorporated - A.F. Gamble - Denver, Colorado, 1956-1962 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Carl C. Farrington - Feed Grains (Speech), 1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Paul L. Farris, Purdue University and Daniel H. McVey, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Article by Farris in Journal of Farm Economics
  - W.S. Farris - Indiana Elevators, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Report from Purdue on elevators
  - Frank G. Rankin - Fat Acidity - Louisville, Kentucky, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Federal Extension Service - Lloyd H. Davis, 1954, 1957, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Federal Extension Service Workshop -Training Course Agricultural - Paul O. Mohn, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Federal Farm Loan Act, Agricultural Credit, Rural Electrification, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Federal Seed Act - Weed Seed Imports - Sig Bjerken, 1960-1968 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Federal Seed Act - Weed Control - Milton R. Young (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Federal Seed Act - Seed Screenings - Milton R. Young, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Federal Trade Commission - Milk Order, 1960-1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Federal Inspection Fee Appeal, Grain Inspection, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Federal Directors - Evanston Region, Fred Maywald - Farmers Grain Dealers Association, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Grain sale
  - Feed Grain Certificate Sales - Charles S. Murphy and Fred Maywald, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Co-Op Feed Grain Meeting, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Feed Grain Meeting, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Feed Grain Program, 1957, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Feed Grain Wheat Proposal - Albert H. Quie, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Feed Grain Programs - Orville L. Freeman, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Feed Grain Program, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Feed Grain Program - Charles S. Murphy, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Wheat and Feed Grain Act of 1962, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Feed Grain Law - Orville L. Freeman, National Grain Trade Council - James G. Patton, M.W. Thatcher, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Special NFGC Memo to Directors, 1959-1968 (Box 47)
  - Memorandum from Bruce J. Henrickson, 1969-1970 (Box 47)
  - Minutes - NFGC Cooperative in Quarterly, 1947-1969 (Box 47)
  - Washington Newsletter (Vol. I-VII), 1946-1952 (Box 48)
  - Washington Newsletter (Vol. VIII-XIV), index Vol. I-XIII, 1954-1960 (Box 49)
  - Washington Newsletter (Vol. XV-XXIII), index Vol. XIV-XXI, 1961-1969 (Box 50)
  - Speech by Roy Hendrickson presented at the 26th Annual Meeting of the Producers Grain Corporation, Amarillo, Texas, 1964; tr - 628 (Box 2940)
  - Speech by Roy Hendrickson presented at the Annual Meeting of the Producers Grain Corporation, Amarillo, Texas, 1966-12; tr - 629 (Box 2940)
  - "Roy Hendrickson at the Capitol", 1956-11-14; MF (Box 2940)
    16 mm Kodachrome, 24 fps, type A film with filter
- Series VI. Chronological Files
  - Jan. 1951 - Dec. 1954, 1951-01-1954-12 (Box 40)
  - Jan. 1955 - July 1957, 1955-01-1957-07 (Box 41)
  - July 1957 - Dec. `959, 1957-07-1959-12 (Box 42)
  - Jan. 1960 - April 1962, 1960-01-1962-04 (Box 43)
  - May 1962 - Oct. 1964, 1962-05-1964-10 (Box 44)
    Missing Nov. - Dec. 1964
  - Jan. 1965 - Dec. 1966, 1965-01-1966-12 (Box 45)
  - Jan. 1967 - Dec. 1968, 1967-01-1968-12 (Box 46)
  - Jan. 1969 - Dec. 1969, 1974 - 1976, Jan 1969 - Dec 1969, 1974-1976 (Box 47)
    Missing Jan. 1970 - Dec. 1973